<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Covid\nSafe</string>
    <string name="main_header_text">Covid\nSafe</string>
    <string name="app_name_one_line">CovidSafe</string>
    <string name="history_header_text">History</string>
    <string name="permissions_header_text"><![CDATA[<font color=#000000>Select your preferences</font>]]></string>
    <string name="health_header_text"><![CDATA[<font color=#000000>Health</font>]]></string>
    <string name="health_header_text_demo"><![CDATA[<font color=#000000>Health [DEMO]</font>]]></string>
    <string name="contact_header_text"><![CDATA[<font color=#000000>Interview Preparation</font>]]></string>
    <string name="contact_header_text_demo"><![CDATA[<font color=#000000>Interview Preparation [DEMO]</font>]]></string>
    <string name="add_symptoms_header_text"><![CDATA[<font color=#000000>Create New Log</font>]]></string>
    <string name="settings_header_text"><![CDATA[<font color=#000000>Settings</font>]]></string>
    <string name="help_header_text"><![CDATA[<font color=#000000>Resources</font>]]></string>
    <string name="help_header_text_demo"><![CDATA[<font color=#000000>Resources [DEMO]</font>]]></string>
    <string name="contact_log_header_text"><![CDATA[<font color=#000000>Contact Log</font>]]></string>
    <string name="contact_log_header_text_demo"><![CDATA[<font color=#000000>Contact Log [DEMO]</font>]]></string>
    <string name="warning_header_text"><![CDATA[<font color=#000000>Diagnosis Report</font>]]></string>
    <string name="symptom_help_text">Use this form to provide a daily report of any symptoms you have. You may submit this form once a day.</string>
    <string name="warning_help_text">You\'ve received a positive diagnosis from your healthcare provider. To confirm your diagnosis, please provider your credentials below.</string>
    <string name="settings_help_text">You can use this panel to create a 1 mile radius around locations you don\'t want to be tracked. You can add up to %1$d locations.</string>
    <string name="notif_message">We are currently logging your location.</string>
    <string name="default_exposed_notif">Based on your location history, we believe you might have been in the same place as people infected with COVID-19.</string>
    <string name="exposed_notif2">Please contact your healthcare professional.</string>

    <string name="contact_title_1">
        Review which symptoms you would like to include.
    </string>
    <string name="contact_title_2">
        Review your location history from the last 14 days.
    </string>
    <string name="contact_title_3">
        Review the people you’ve been in contact with recently.
    </string>
    <string name="contact_title_4">
        Save this list for reference during your interview.
    </string>
    <string name="contact_desc_1">
        We’ve detected severe symptoms in your recent reports, and collected them below.
    </string>
    <string name="contact_desc_2">
        Below are locations you’ve recently visited for 10 minutes or more. This helps us track locations that might be high-risk for exposure.
    </string>
    <string name="contact_desc_3">
        Below you can add a list of people you’ve been in close contact with (6m) for 10 or more minutes in the last 14 days.
    </string>
    <string name="contact_desc_4">
        Don’t worry, you can always come back to edit this list later. You can export this information into an email record for yourself.
    </string>

    <string name="q1">
        What is the purpose of this app?
    </string>
    <string name="a1">
        CovidSafe is an app that seeks to reduce the spread of coronavirus in the community, specifically by helping people learn if they\'ve been exposed, connecting them to the appropriate public health guidance, and by enabling effective contact tracing. CovidSafe also reduces the burden on public health systems by offering people who have been positively diagnosed and their potential exposures, a safe, private, and fast way to communicate this information to the people who need it — public health authorities and their contact tracing teams.
    </string>
    <string name="q2">
        How does this app benefit me?
    </string>
    <string name="a2">
        CovidSafe offers several features to protect both you and your community:\n
        •	Get notified about possible exposure. You may be notified if someone who was near you within the last two weeks has come down with symptoms of COVID-19. The measure of \‘near\’ is not as precise as the medical definition (within 6 feet for more than 10 minutes), but it is accurate up to a few meters.\n
        •	Track your symptoms. The symptoms you track may be useful to assist public health teams if you are confirmed positive, and for having this information readily available if you are exposed and called for a contact tracing interview. You can also get reliable, vetted information about SARS-CoV-2, why it\'s so dangerous, and how it spreads.
    </string>
    <string name="q3">
        Who can use CovidSafe?
    </string>
    <string name="a3">
        When it becomes available for use, CovidSafe is free, and anyone can use it.
    </string>
    <string name="q4">
        Who else benefits from my participation with this app?
    </string>
    <string name="a4">
        CovidSafe is capable of alerting people who have been in areas where coronavirus is active. If you test positive for coronavirus, you\'ll also be able to anonymously notify others you may have been in contact with over the past two weeks to alert them that they may have been exposed, and to prepare them for potential contact tracing interviews.
    </string>
    <string name="q5">
        How does CovidSafe help public health officials?
    </string>
    <string name="a5">
        Traditional contact tracing interviews done by public health services are important, laborious, complicated and can sometimes omit important contacts because patients forget to mention them. CovidSafe helps people who have tested positive remember locations they’ve visited recently, by providing an objective log, which they can then share with contact tracing teams. There is also functionality to organize the contact information of known contacts, which streamlines the interview process and enables contact tracers to work faster.
    </string>

<!--    privacy-->
    <string name="pq1">
        If I test positive and I disclose it via CovidSafe, what information is revealed to others?
    </string>
    <string name="pa1">
        Other people with the application, who have been exposed may be notified, along with the time the exposure occurred. No other information will be revealed.
    </string>
    <string name="pq2">
        If I test negative, can a malicious person get access to my phone’s broadcasts and report me as being positive?
    </string>
    <string name="pa2">
        No, this isn’t possible. The app is encrypted to prevent it from happening using similar security technology used for other purposes, such as online banking.
    </string>
    <string name="pq3">
        If someone else obtains data used to alert people who have been exposed, what can they learn?
    </string>
    <string name="pa3">
        They\'ll see a sequence of random identifiers that have been broadcast over time near people who have tested positive for coronavirus. They could assume the location of the person who tested positive if the random identifiers were collected at specific locations. Otherwise, the person remains anonymous. The security of the system relies on the fact this data can be made public without compromising privacy.
    </string>
    <string name="pq4">
        If I receive a message that I have been exposed, what is disclosed to the public?
    </string>
    <string name="pa4">
        Nothing about your identity will be disclosed to the public.
    </string>
    <string name="pq5">
        Can the identity of a person who chooses to report they’ve tested positive be guessed by others?
    </string>
    <string name="pa5">
        Possibly. A person who was near someone who has tested positive may be able to guess the infected person\'s identity. If there are two or more people who were near someone who has tested positive, the process of identifying the infected person may be easier. However, the person\'s identity will never be broadcast directly. People’s identities aren’t stored in the data. Only the infected person’s random broadcast is stored.
    </string>
    <string name="pq6">
        What data is stored on my phone? What data about me is stored publicly?
    </string>
    <string name="pa6">
        Each phone broadcasts a random signal (using Bluetooth) to other nearby phones. All phones remember the signals they send and receive for two weeks. These broadcast signals can be thought of as non-identifying random numbers. The signal each phone broadcasts changes, so the signals remain anonymous and can’t be linked to a specific person. If someone tests positive and chooses to disclose this information to help others, they would be disclosing only their phone\'s broadcasts for the past two weeks. This lets other people using CovidSafe check if they were near the infected person to determine if they were exposed, based on their own phones\' broadcasts.
    </string>
    <string name="pq7">
        How does location tracking work?
    </string>
    <string name="pa7">
        See the Bluetooth section in the PACT white paper on our website.
    </string>
    <string name="pq8">
        Will this information be shared with government agencies?
    </string>
    <string name="pa8">
        The tool won\'t alert government agencies about your identity if you\'re exposed.
    </string>
    <string name="pq9">
        Why should I report my illness?
    </string>
    <string name="pa9">
        If you become ill, you can use the app to improve the efficiency and completeness of manual contact tracing interviews. Your privacy is maximized by ensuring that all the data remains on your device, except for what you voluntarily reveal to healthcare authorities to enable more effective contact tracing.
    </string>
<!---->

    <string name="aq1">
        What is contact tracing?
    </string>
    <string name="aa1">
Contact tracing is a process that helps identify all the people who may have come into contact with a person who is ill. Traditionally, contact tracing is accomplished by public health workers interviewing the person who is ill to learn about people they’ve been in contact with and locations they\'ve recently visited within a specific period of time, such as the past two weeks. With CovidSafe, tracing is done through the app instead of in person.
    </string>
    <string name="aq2">
        Why should I report my illness?
    </string>
    <string name="aa2">
        If you become ill, you can use the app to improve the efficiency and completeness of manual contact tracing interviews. Your privacy is maximized by ensuring that all the data remains on your device, except for what you voluntarily reveal to healthcare authorities to enable contact tracing.
    </string>


    <string name="certError">Please check the box to certify that all the information in this form is correct.</string>
    <string name="noneCheckedError">Please check at least one symptom.</string>
    <string name="addressError">The address you have entered is invalid. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="maxBlacklistSizeError">Maximum blacklist size reached.</string>
    <string name="perm_error">Location access must be enabled at all times for tracking to take place. Please try again.</string>

    <string name="prompt_to_enable_error">Enable Bluetooth and GPS in settings to start logging.</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_is_off">Bluetooth is currently turned off.</string>
    <string name="pos_text">Positive COVID-19 Diagnosis Reported</string>

    <string name="public_key_pkey">public_key_pkey</string>
    <string name="last_refresh_date_pkey">last_refresh_date_pkey</string>
    <string name="last_submission_date_pkey">last_submission_date</string>
    <string name="broadcasting_enabled_pkey">broadcasting</string>
    <string name="gps_enabled_pkey">gpsEnabled</string>
    <string name="ble_enabled_pkey">bleEnabled</string>
    <string name="onboard_enabled_pkey">prefs_onboard</string>
    <string name="notifs_enabled_pkey">prefs_notifs</string>
    <string name="most_recent_seed_pkey">most_recent_seed_pkey</string>
    <string name="most_recent_seed_timestamp_pkey">most_recent_seed_timestamp_pkey</string>
    <string name="diagnosis_pkey">prefs_diagnosis_date</string>
    <string name="symptom_submission_date_pkey">symptom_submission_date_pkey</string>
    <string name="time_of_last_query_pkey">time_of_last_query_pkey</string>
    <string name="notif_id_pkey">notif_id_pkey</string>
    <string name="init_key_exists_pkey">init_key_exists_pkey</string>
    <string name="aes_key_pkey">aes_key_pkey</string>
    <string name="aes_iv_pkey">aes_iv_pkey</string>
    <string name="infection_window_in_days_pkeys">infection_window_in_days_pkeys</string>
    <string name="quarantine_end_time_pkey">quarantine_end_time_pkey</string>
    <string name="last_symptom_update_pkey">last_symptom_update_pkey</string>

    <string name="phone">911</string>
    <string name="privacyDisclaimer">Any information collected on CovidSafe is stored securely and locally in your app, and remain private to you.</string>
    <string name="privacyDisclaimer2">This information is stored securely and locally on your app, and remains private to you.</string>
    <string name="perm_gps_rationale">Without this permission, we will be unable to capture location information. Are you sure you want to deny this permission?</string>
    <string name="perm_gps_ask">We require access to location information when the app is closed. Would you like to open app settings to enable this?</string>

    <string name="perm_ble_rationale">Without this permission, we will be unable to capture Bluetooth information of users around you. Are you sure you want to deny this permission?</string>
    <string name="perm_ble_ask">We require access to Bluetooth information when the app is closed. Would you like to open app settings to enable this?</string>

    <string name="perm_contacts_rationale">Without this permission, we will be unable to add contacts to the app. Are you sure you want to deny this permission?</string>

    <string name="perm_notifs_rationale">Without this permission, we will be unable to send you notifications. Are you sure you want to deny this permission?</string>
    <string name="perm_notifs_ask">We require push notifications to be enabled. Would you like to open app settings to enable this?</string>

    <string name="perm_loc_rationale">Without this permission, we will be unable to track your location when the app is closed. Are you sure you want to deny this permission?</string>
    <string name="perm_loc_ask">We require access to location information when the app is closed. Would you like to open app settings to enable this?</string>

    <string name="tip_desc_1">
        Everyone with COVID-19 symptoms (fever, cough, and/or difficulty breathing) who has a test result pending, shall stay in an quarantine location (your home if you have one or in a government directed or publicly provided location if one is available) in accordance with CDC and Public Health guidance.\n\n
        If your test result is positive, you must then remain in isolation.
    </string>

    <string name="tip_desc_2">
        Not everybody who feels ill needs to be tested, particularly if you have mild illness. Healthcare providers determine who should be tested. While testing is becoming more available, there are still limitations in the ability to quickly collect and process tests.\n\n        If you are sick with fever, cough or shortness of breath and are in a high risk group, call your healthcare provider to discuss whether you should be tested for COVID-19.
    </string>

    <string name="tip_desc_3">
        If you have symptoms like cough, fever, or other respiratory problems, contact your regular doctor first. <b>Do not go to the emergency room.</b> Emergency rooms need to be able to serve those with the most critical needs. If you have difficulty breathing, it doesn’t mean you have novel coronavirus, but you should call 911.
    </string>

    <string name="risk_low">No known transmission vectors</string>
    <string name="risk_high">Risk of transmission</string>

    <string name="start">Start logging</string>
    <string name="stop">Stop logging</string>

    <string name="ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="retry">Retry</string>
    <string name="sure">I\'m sure</string>

    <string name="logging">Limited trace data is being collected. We keep your identity anonymous.<![CDATA[<font color=#8d55e9><br/><b><a href="https://covidsafe.cs.washington.edu/">Learn More</a></b></font>]]></string>
    <string name="stopping">Turn broadcasting on to improve the accuracy of your notifications. <![CDATA[<font color=#8d55e9><br/><b><a href="https://covidsafe.cs.washington.edu/">Learn More</a></b></font>]]></string>

    <string name="kingCountyLink">https://kingcounty.gov/depts/health/communicable-diseases/disease-control/novel-coronavirus.aspx</string>
    <string name="covidSiteLink">https://covidsafe.cs.washington.edu/</string>
    <string name="covidSiteFaqLink">https://covidsafe.cs.washington.edu/#faq</string>
    <string name="privacyLink1"><![CDATA[<font color=#8d55e9><a href="https://covidsafe.cs.washington.edu/">Learn more.</a></font>]]></string>
    <string name="privacy_link"><![CDATA[<font color=#FFFFFF><a href="http://www.uw.edu">Privacy  |  </a></font>]]></string>
    <string name="terms_link"><![CDATA[<font color=#FFFFFF><a href="http://www.uw.edu">Terms and Conditions</a></font>]]></string>

    <string name="lipsum">Egestas tellus rutrum tellus pellentesque eu tincidun. Odio tempor orci dapibus ultrices in iaculis nunc sed augue suspendisse.</string>
    <string name="lipsum2">Egestas tellus rutrum tellus pellentesque eu tincidunt. Odio tempor orci dapibus ultrices in iaculis nunc sed augue.</string>
    <string name="lipsum3">Odio tempor orci dapibus ultrices in iaculis nunc sed</string>
    <string name="lipsum4">Egestas tellus rutrum tellus pellentesque eu tincidunt. Odio tempor orci dapibus ultrices in iaculis nunc sed augue.</string>
    <string name="lipsum5">Egestas tellus rutrum tellus ultrices in iaculis pellentesque eu tincidunt?</string>
    <string name="lipsum6">Odio tempor orci dapibus ultrices in iaculis </string>
    <string name="privacyText">
        Learn more
    </string>
    <string name="permissionsHeader">
        Enable real-time notifications to get alerts about potential exposures and public health messages relevant to you.\n\nCovidSafe reveals no information about you without your consent.
    </string>

    <string name="perm1">Notifications</string>
    <string name="perm2">Location Logging</string>
    <string name="perm3">Bluetooth Tracing</string>

    <string name="perm1desc">
        Receive notifications for exposure risks in your area.
    </string>
    <string name="perm2desc">
        Receive announcements and notifications relevant to your neighborhood. All location information is stored locally.
    </string>
    <string name="perm3desc">
        Emit and detect random numbers by Bluetooth to later discover exposure risks.
    </string>

    <string name="setting1">Length of data storage</string>
    <string name="setting1desc">Number of days until local logs are automatically deleted.</string>

    <string name="storyTitle1">
        Welcome to CovidSafe
    </string>
    <string name="storyTitle2">
        Exposure Notifications
    </string>
    <string name="storyTitle3">
        Self-Care Tips
    </string>
    <string name="storyTitle4">
        Your Privacy
    </string>

    <string name="story1">
        CovidSafe notifies you if you may have been exposed to coronavirus and helps keep you and your community safer.
    </string>
    <string name="story2">
        Learn if you might have been exposed. If you\'ve recently been in close contact with someone recently diagnosed with COVID-19. You\'ll get a notification.
    </string>
    <string name="story3">
        Take care of yourself and others. Get self-care tips, connect with the appropriate public health guidance if you\'ve experienced symptoms. And log locations you recently visited to protect others.
    </string>
    <string name="story4">
        Any information you contribute is protected. Learn more about how your information is used and protected on the Privacy page in Settings.
    </string>
    <string name="startText">
        Let\s slow the spread of COVID-19 together.
    </string>

    <string name="emergency">
        Stop and call 911 if you are experiencing:\n
        • Severe, constant chest pain or pressure\n
        • Extreme difficulty breathing\n
        • Severe, constant lightheadedness\n
        • Serious disorientation or unresponsiveness
    </string>

    <string name="symptom1">Fever</string>
    <string name="symptom2">Cough</string>
    <string name="symptom3">Shortness of breath</string>
    <string name="symptom4">Trouble breathing</string>
    <string name="symptom5">Persistent pain or pressure in the chest</string>
    <string name="symptom6">New confusion or inability to arouse</string>
    <string name="symptom7">Bluish lips or face</string>
    <string name="certText">I certify that the information submitted in this report is true and correct to the best of my knowledge.</string>
    <string name="certDiagnosisText">I certify that I have been officially diagnosed with COVID-19</string>
</resources>
